https://kagomeusa.com/privacy-policy/

Hit enter to search or ESC to close
PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Kagome USA.
Information Collection and Use
Kagome USA is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Kagome USA collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
Website Registration
In order to use some features of this website, users must first complete the registration form. During registration, users are required to give their contact information (name and e-mail address). This information is used to contact users about the topics on our site for which they have expressed interest and to enable users to retrieve lost passwords. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (mailing address, position, technical skill, etc.).
Cookies
Kagome USA uses cookies to remember if users have logged in while on our site. This allows website users to avoid logging in more than once, thereby saving time. Users have the option of disabling or not accepting cookies by changing the preferences on their browsers*. If users opt to disable cookies, they will still be able to use our website. However, they will not be able to use some functionality or post to the message boards. No personally identifiable information (e-mail address, name, etc.) is collected with the cookies that we set. Accepting cookies while on the Kagome USA site will not put the user at risk for marketing to other sites. *Different browsers have different cookie settings. With Netscape, you can ask the browser to allow, warn you, or completely disable cookies. Internet Explorer has an additional feature where you can specify different settings for different security zones. You can choose to allow websites to create cookies for you in your “trusted sites” (like Kagome USA), to warn you before you create them in your local Intranet zone, and to give you an option to never allow them in a “restricted zone.” See the “Help” section of your particular browser for more information on working with cookies.
Web Statistics
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use for reporting and sponsorship purposes. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Kagome USA does not claim any responsibility for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information, and we have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Surveys
Occasionally, our site requests information from users via Web surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include demographic data (such as zip code and age), but nothing that can identify any individual person will be collected. Survey results will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Choice/Opt-in
Our users are given the opportunity to “opt in” to newsletters and site update e-mail messages. To unsubscribe from mailings, please see that section above. To unsubscribe from any updates, users can use the “edit my profile” link from their homepage. To avoid receiving certain topic updates, the user can simply deselect the topics and select the “modify” button. Notification of Changes If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
© 2020 KAGOME USA
SUSTAINABILITY |
PRIVACY | CAREERS |
About Us
Kagome History
Facilities & Locations
Kagome Milestones
Our Process
Interested in this sauce?
We’d love to talk to you!
ssf here
No thanks, just download the PDF.
CLOSE
Interested in this sauce?
We’d love to talk to you!
ssf here
No thanks, just download the PDF.
CLOSE
Interested in this sauce?
We’d love to talk to you!
ssf here
No thanks, just download the PDF.
CLOSE
Interested in this sauce?
We’d love to talk to you!
ssf here
No thanks, just download the PDF.
CLOSE
Interested in this sauce?
We’d love to talk to you!
ssf here
No thanks, just download the PDF.
CLOSE
Interested in this sauce?
We’d love to talk to you!
ssf here
No thanks, just download the PDF.
CLOSE
Interested in this sauce?
We’d love to talk to you!
ssf here
No thanks, just download the PDF.
CLOSE
Interested in this sauce?
We’d love to talk to you!
No thanks, just download the PDF.
CLOSE
